This lesson is divided into three parts.
本课程分成3部分
You have the extract part which starts here,
开始是数据提取部分
and then you have transform,
接下来是数据转换部分
and then finally here at the bottom you have
最下面是数据加载部分
load and then that is followed by an exercise that puts ETL altogether.
之后是一个将 ETL 组合在一起的练习
Throughout the lesson, you'll be working through
课程中 你将完成
exercises that use data from the World Bank.
一系列来自世界银行数据的练习
Although, you won't be running any machine learning algorithms, in this lesson,
尽管本课程中你不需要运行任何机器学习算法
you'll be preparing data for a task such as linear regression,
但是你要准备给模型的数据 如线性回归模型
this is the World Bank's project website.
这是世界银行项目的官网
The World Bank has quite a bit of data that you can download.
世界银行有很多数据供你下载
In this lesson, you'll work with data from
本课程中 你将使用
the World Bank projects database and the World Bank indicators database.
来自世界银行项目数据库和世界银行指标数据库的数据
For example, each World Bank Project has a cost associated with
例如 世界银行项目数据库有一项是相关的金额
it as well as other data like the project title and project theme.
还有其他数据 如项目名称和项目主题
The indicator data with the World Bank has
世界银行的指标数据有
socio-demographic information and financial data about countries around the world.
全世界各国家的社会人口信息和金融数据
Say, if you're going to try to predict the cost of a World Bank project,
比如 如果你打算尝试预测世界银行项目的花销
you might want to see if the socio-demographic or financial country data
你可能想要看看社会人口信息和金融数据
made good features.
是不是好的特征
You'd have to combine data together from the projects dataset as
你需要将项目数据集和
well as this socio demographic data.
社会人口数据整合到一起
Again, you won't actually be trying to make these predictions.
再次声明 你不需要真的尝试预测
Instead, you'll be putting the data through
你需要让数据通过
an ETL pipeline to get the data ready for analysis.
ETL 管道以便于分析
Let me just give you a better overview of where this data comes from.
让我更详细介绍一下数据的来源
So back here, this website has information
回到这里 网站有所有
about all of the projects that the World Bank finances.
世界银行资助的项目的信息
If you scroll down here,
窗口向下滚动到这里
and go to use our data and click and then you go to data and resources,
点击“使用我们的数据” 然后你就会了解到数据和资料
you can download the projects data in different formats.
你能下载各种格式的项目数据
For example, they have a project's API and they also have a CSV file.
例如 他们提供一个项目数据 API  他们还提供CSV 文件
So, what I did for this lesson was I
所以 我们这里做的是
downloaded the CSV file and used it in the classroom.
下载 CSV 文件 并在教室中使用
You're not going to actually have to download data from
你不需要从官网下载数据
this website because I've already done it and set it up for you.
因为我们已经帮你下载和部署好了
So, the World Bank has another data repository for country indicator data.
世界银行还有另一个国家指标数据的数据仓库
Indicators are things like GDP,
指标包括像 GDP
percent of a population that is rural,
农村人口比例
and other demographic and economic information.
以及其他的人口和经济信息
To give an example,
举例来说
you'll be working with GDP data.
你想要获取 GDP 数据.
You can go here to the search bar and put in GDP,
你可以到搜索框 输入 GDP
and then it says GP current US dollar and then
它会显示 GDP (US$)
there are bunch of other ways that they measure GDP.
还有一些其他的衡量GDP的方式
So, I'm going to click here on top.
我点击最上面的这里
Then there's a graphical user interface where you can play around with the data.
就出现了一个图形界面 你可以在这里查看数据
But all I did was go here to the side where it says download and then I would just
但我要做的仅仅是移到右边 这里显示下载
click on whatever format I wanted and download the data.
点击你想下载的格式 然后下载数据
Again, I've said it all up for you in the classroom
重申一下 我之前说过数据已经帮你准备好了
so you don't actually have to download this data yourself.
所以你不需要真的自己再下载一遍
Notice as well, up here in the web URL,
还要注意 在上面的网络 URL
it says NY, GDP, and KTPCD.
显示 NY.GDP.MKTP.CD
So, that is some sort of abbreviation the World Bank uses to represent GDP.
这是某种世界银行规定的缩写方式表示GDP
Going back to the classroom,
回到教室
the exercises are marked here on the left as an exercise.
所有的练习都在左侧标记好了练习字样
So for example, if you clicked on extract
例如 如果你点击这个 数据提取
here that would be just information there might be text in
会显示文字和视频信息
a video and then you'll click on exercise CSV which will open
如果你点击 练习：CSV
an exercise with a Jupiter notebook and then you can start working.
会显示一个Jupyter notebook 里面是练习题 需要你完成
So, that's where the data comes from for this lesson and that's
好的 这就是本课程的数据来源
how all of the exercises are organized.
以及所有安排的练习